Guide to the Duke Student Government Reference Collection, 1993-[ongoing]
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Duke Student Government Reference collection 1993-[ongoing]
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.5 Linear Feet 250 Items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Duke Student Government Reference Collection was compiled from various sources by University Archives staff for reference and research.
Historical Note
The Duke Student Government (DSG) replaced the existing student government Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), in 1993 under a new organization in which the legislative and executive branches were consolidated.
Collection Overview
The Duke Student Government Reference Collection contains files of clippings, articles, printouts, publications, and other materials about student participation in univerity administration through Duke Student Government. Topics include alcohol, elections, off-campus housing, proposals and resolutions, and presidents and officers. This collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Student Government
Duke University -- Students
Duke University. University Archives.
Student participation in administration.
Related Material
Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965-1993.
University Archives, Duke University.
Duke Student Government Records, 1983-2003.
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Container List, 1 Box
  - Alcohol (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 1998-
  - Elections, 2001-
  - History, 1993-
  - Miscellaneous
  - Newsletter: The DSG Agenda, 1996-1997
  - Printed Matters: Off-Campus Housing Guide, 1997
  - Presidents and Officers, 1993
  - Proposals
  - Resolutions